[
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "What is the French word for 'apple'?",
    "options": ["le chien", "la pomme", "le lait", "la table"],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Which one means 'bread'?",
    "options": ["le pain", "la porte", "le livre", "le chocolat"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Choose the correct translation for 'the chair'.",
    "options": ["la chaise", "le chat", "la chemise", "le fromage"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "type": "type",
    "question": "Type the French word for 'le lait'.",
    "answer": "milk",
    "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
    "type": "type",
    "question": "Type the French word for 'le crayon'.",
    "answer": "pencil",
    "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Which word means 'the book'?",
    "options": ["le livre", "la fenêtre", "le jardin", "la cuisine"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "type": "type",
    "question": "Type the English word for 'le fromage'.",
    "answer": "cheese",
    "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
  "type": "mcq",
  "question": "Which word means 'the fish'?",
  "options": ["le poisson", "le chien", "la table", "la voiture"],
  "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "type": "type",
    "question": "Type the English word for 'la table'.",
    "answer": "table",
    "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
    "type": "type",
    "question": "Type the English word for 'œuf'.",
    "answer": "egg",
    "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
    "type": "type",
    "question": "Type the English word for 'bœuf'.",
    "answer": "beef",
    "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
  "type": "mcq",
  "question": "Which word means 'the tomato'?",
  "options": ["le citron", "la pomme", "le fromage", "la tomate"],
  "answerIndex": 3
  },
  {
  "type": "mcq",
  "question": "Which word means 'the banana'?",
  "options": ["la carotte", "le raisin", "la banane", "le pain"],
  "answerIndex": 2
  },
  {
  "type": "type",
  "question": "Type the English word for 'brocoli'.",
  "answer": "broccoli",
  "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
  "type": "type",
  "question": "Type the English word for 'la glace'.",
  "answer": "ice cream",
  "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
  "type": "mcq",
  "question": "Which word means 'the cookie'?",
  "options": ["la tarte", "le biscuit", "le gâteau", "la confiture"],
  "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Which word means 'the napkin'?",
    "options": ["le couteau", "la serviette", "la fourchette", "l'assiette"],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "type": "type",
    "question": "Type the English word for 'l'assiette'.",
    "answer": "plate",
    "characterLimit": 15
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Which word means 'the spoon'?",
    "options": ["la fourchette", "le couteau", "la cuillère", "le plat"],
    "answerIndex": 2
  }
]
